[
    {
        "question": "According to paragraph 2, the process of visual perception ............",
        "options": [
            "is not the same for all people",
            "begins with patterns of light",
            "is not very scientific",
            "requires other senses to function"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What did Matisse reinterpret?",
        "options": [
            "A goddess from mythology",
            "A painting by another artist",
            "An ancient sculpture",
            "A man in history"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The word \"them\" in the last paragraph refers to .............",
        "options": [
            "each attentive observer",
            "thoughts and emotions",
            "a lifetime of experiences",
            "great works of art"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The word \"bequeath\" in thepassage is closest in meaning to ...................",
        "options": ["make out", "pass on", "look over", "take in"],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The author mentions all of the following ways to enhance the appreciation of art EXCEPT ...................",
        "options": [
            "understanding the artistic process",
            "becoming familiar with the history",
            "experiencing the art by copying",
            "knowing about the life of the artist"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main topic of this passage?",
        "options": [
            "Visual perception of sensory material",
            "The historical context for artistic expression",
            "Studying.Van Gogh's The Starry Night",
            "The appreciation of works of art"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the sentences below best expresses the information in the highlighted statement in the passage?",
        "options": [
            "We see images differently because of the mode of perception.",
            "Although we see images differently, the mode of perception is similar.",
            "Since the mode of perception is similar, we see images in the same way.",
            "When the mode of perception is the same, we see the same images"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Why might Van Gogh have painted The Starry Night?",
        "options": [
            "To symbolizelthe journey of life after death",
            "To create a dramatic contrast with the sky",
            "To place a strong image in the foreground",
            "To include nature from his early experience"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The word intrigued‚Äù in the passage is closest in meaning to ................",
        "options": [
            "very pleased",
            "very confused",
            "very interested",
            "very surprised"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What can be inferred from the last paragraph?",
        "options": [
            "Greatest artworks are impossible to understand.",
            "The author shows negative feelings toward contemporary art.",
            "People need knowledge to understand art.",
            "What we see in art is determined by our emotions, experiences, and thoughts."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    }
]
